Hello everyone, in this video we will learn how to use the video capture function.
Through the video capture function, you can capture the animation seen in the 3D window into a video.
You can use the main menu animation video capture or go to the animation editor tool bar to find this function.
First, please set the starting point and end point of the play area.
Then click on the video capture button to start recording.
When capturing the video, the video capture button will become the stop button.
You can click on this button to stop the video capture.
When the video capture is automatically finished or stopped, the captured video will automatically be played in your default player.
In the video capture setting, you can choose the size of the video to capture according to your needs.
When selecting a custom image, you can freely set the size.
If you choose full screen, the size of the video will be the size of your display.
For window, the size of the 3D window is the size of the video.
You can choose the format to save under the file selection.
You can choose to save the captured video as a file.
After selecting this option, you can set the name of the video and save the path.
After setting, click on Capture.
Please note that video capture is not possible without animation.
In addition, the video capture function is based on the 3D window.
The current lens captures the video, so you can only capture the animation seen in the current 3D window.
Thank you for watching. See you in the next video.
Thank you for watching.